#### SHREE HARSHA SRIDHARAMURTHY

(812)-349-8449 sridhash@iu.edu 3209 E 10th St. Apt E9, Bloomington, IN 47408

www.shreeharsha.me linkedin.com/in/sshreeharsha

## **Qualifications Summary**

Computer science graduate student with interest in intelligent software engineering and web development. Professional experience of 6+ years in building enterprise full stack web applications, leading team of size 3. Research experience of 11 months with School of Public and Environmental Affairs.

#### Education

Indiana University, Bloomington, IN

May 2017 (expected)

Master of Science - Computer Science

Visveswaraya Technological University, Belgaum, India

June 2009

Bachelor of Engineering - Computer Science

# Technical Skills

Web Development: HTML5, jQuery, CSS, XML, PHP, ASP.NET, SharePoint Server 2010, Bootstrap

**Programming Languages:** C#, Java, C++, Python

Databases: MS SQL Server, Oracle

Applications: Visual Studio 2015, Eclipse, Nintex, Tableau, Business Objects, Informatica PowerDesigner

Platforms: Unix, Citrix, Oracle VirtualBox

## Professional Experience

Graduate Research Assistant | Indiana University | Bloomington, Indiana Nov 2015 – Present

• Waterworks - received competitive research grant from Indiana University Office of Sustainability for developing game to educate players in water systems thinking. [HTML5, jQuery, PHP, Bootstrap]

Web Developer, Auxiliary IT | Indiana University | Bloomington, Indiana Jan 2016 - May 2016

• Designed front end user interface with workflows for custom portals. [SharePoint Server 2010, Nintex]

I.T. Analyst | Tata Consultancy Services | Bangalore, India

Aug 2013 – Jul 2015

- Received department-wide appreciation for developing rich and responsive portal visited by 3000 users. [SharePoint Server 2010, jQuery, CSS, BootstrapTour]
- Programmatically bridged incompatible platforms, adding https (SSL), Single Sign On (SSO) Identity and Access Management (I&AM) abilities as lead developer of SAP implementation projects tracking tool. [C#, SharePoint Server 2010, SAML2.0, ASP.NET, jQuery]

Senior Systems Engineer | Infosys Limited | Bangalore, India

Jan 2009 - Aug 2013

- Performance tuned and reduced deployment costs by 50% by redesigning and migrating 4 custom built applications to SharePoint platform. [ASP.NET, SharePoint Server 2010, jQuery]
- Single-handedly enhanced 14 websites built over multiple technologies, for Pfizer's intranet. [C#, Java, Unix, ASP.NET, SharePoint Server 2010, MOSS 2007, Informatica PowerDesigner, Business Objects, Windows Batch Scripting

# Academic Projects

• PageRank algorithm implementation on distributed systems.

[Java, MPJ Express]

• Backend programming on SQLite database for Android app. • Asymptotic analysis of string matching algorithms.

[Core Java, XML]

• Project on comparative analysis of classification algorithms.

[C#, C++][Python, Tableau, Weka, Scikit, Unix]

• Movie recommendation system and decision tree classifier.

[Python, R, C#]

• Artificial intelligence based games Rameses, Yahtzee and map coloring program.

[Python, Java]

• XINU kernel deployment on Beaglebone Black with process management and networking. [C, Bash]

# **Activities and Honors**

$\bullet$ Research and development grant (\$10,000) from Indiana University Office of Sustainability.	2016
• Merit award from IU.	$\boldsymbol{2015}$
• Appreciation from department head at Tata Consultancy Services.	<b>2015</b>
• Introduced game programming to public as a Science volunteer at Indiana University.	2015
• Team rated 7 of 7 by client-partner Pfizer for robust application development.	2013
• Most Valuable Player award - Superior performance at Infosys.	2012
• Most Valuable Player award - Best Debutante at Infosys.	2010